licd.com 2007-02-02

# Least I Could Do » Home Page

|  |  |   
---|---  
  
Privacy Policy  

Blind Ferret Entertainment, producer of Least I Could Do and its related content and service sites, believes that electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. We know you're concerned about protecting your privacy online. At Blind Ferret, we treat your personal information (especially payment information) with the highest standards of safety, security, and confidentiality. ________________________________________   
**Information Gathered**   
We don't collect personal information without your knowledge. We don't sell, rent, or give your personal information to unrelated third parties without your prior permission. This policy explains what information we collect about you and how we use that information. We also outline the choices you have.   
________________________________________   
**Least I Could Do Store**   
By shopping at www.leasticoulddo.com, you accept the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. In order to ship products to you, we need to collect information about you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, home phone number and credit card information. We use your e-mail address as a login for the store, as well as a way to send you a confirmation of your order. If we have a question about your order, we may contact you by e-mail or by phone. For example, we may call you to verify your credit card information on a large purchase. We do this for your protection. You can change your personal information at any time by clicking the "my account" button and login with your e-mail address and password. There, you can modify your account information.   
________________________________________   
**Cookies**   
The Least I Could Do store does not require the use of cookies. However, we offer it as a convenient way for our store to confirm your identity and keep items in your shopping cart if you leave the site. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Blind Ferret cannot and does not control these cookies.   
________________________________________   
**Security**   
Blind Ferret pledges a safe and worry-free shopping experience. We use the industry standard for Internet security, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL 128-bit) encryption to protect your personal data and ensure that it is transmitted securely.   
________________________________________   
**Traffic Data**   
Each time a visitor comes to a Blind Ferret Entertainment site, information is collected to improve the overall quality of Blind Ferret sites. Blind Ferret Entertainment collects the visitor's domain name/IP Address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from netscape.com or yale.edu or 255.255.255.0), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to an Blind Ferret Entertainment site), and browser/platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). In addition to collecting these types of information, Blind Ferret Entertainment's advertisement delivery system collects aggregate search terms for internal reporting and targeted advertising. Blind Ferret Entertainment's advertisement delivery system collects visitor information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising. Blind Ferret Entertainment also counts, tracks, and aggregates the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flow at Blind Ferret sites (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from and how traffic flows within the sites). Blind Ferret Entertainment may merge this information into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners. Blind Ferret Entertainment will not disclose your individual identity or personal data. When Blind Ferret Entertainment does present aggregated information to potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.   
________________________________________   
**E-mail Services**   
Any/all e-mail addresses sent to us as the result of correspondence with the consumers of Blind Ferret Entertainment will not be used or collected for the purposes of reselling to a third party and will not be added to a bulk e-mailing list. Blind Ferret provides users the opportunity to opt-in and opt-out of receiving e-mail communications from us. This is made available during sign-up for our e-mail lists and in e-mail messages delivered from Blind Ferret. For any list managed by Blind Ferret, users can use the link in the footer of most e-mail messages to unsubscribe.   
________________________________________   
**Sharing and Usage Of Information**   
Blind Ferret never shares, sells, or rents any personal information without your permission, unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information.   
________________________________________   
**Copyright**

**Least I Could Do®** is a web comic published by Blind Ferret Entertainment 

**Blind Ferret Entertainment®** uses invented names in all its stories, except in cases when public figures are being satirized. Any other use of real names is accidental and coincidental. 

The content of this web-site-graphics, text and other elements-is © Copyright 2004 by Blind Ferret Entertainment, and may not be reprinted or retransmitted in whole or in part without the expressed written consent of the publisher. 

**Least I Could Do®** is not intended for readers under 18 years of age. 

|  |  All content & images are © Blind Ferret Entertainment.  
[Privacy Policy](http://www.leasticoulddo.com/privacy_policy.php) | [Advertising](http://www.leasticoulddo.com/advertise.php) |  Site design by Leaking Faucet Studio  
Webmasters: Scot Lincicome and Ryan McCahan   
---|---  
  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
|  Log into your Forum Account.

Username:   
Password:  

|   
  
|  |   
---|---|---  

|  |
